footyheadlines.com 2018-06-08

# Footy Headlines: Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy explain how we collect, use, and share information we obtain through your use of Footy Headlines. By using the Services, you explicitly consent to such use of your information and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you have any further questions regarding the Privace Policy you can [contact us](http://www.footyheadlines.com/p/footy-headlines-contact-form.html).

Effective Date: November 16, 2013

## Cookies

We may set and access cookies on your computer. Upon your first visit to Footy Headlines, a cookie is sent to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. A "cookie" is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer and stored on your hard drive when you visit a website. Each web site can send its own cookie to your browser. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies.

We also may allow certain analytic services and providers of applications used on the Services (e.g., sharing buttons) to collect Non-Personally Identifiable information by placing cookies on the Services that will track certain performance of our Services, such as, web traffic, click-throughs, etc.

## Third Part Cookies

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website.

Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.

You can opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) or opt out of Google Analytics visiting the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). 

## Use of Analytics Tools

We are using Analytics Tools such as Google Analytics and DoubleClick Cookies to understand how our users use Footy Headlines. We are only collecting non-personal infomations.

Each time you visit Footy Headlines we collect your IP address, browser and computer type, access time, the Web page you came from, the URL you go to next, and the Web pages that you access during your visit.

You can opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) or opt out of Google Analytics visiting the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). 

## Links

Footy Headlines contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any such other website and urge you to review such practices prior to submitting any information to such websites.

## Questions

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us.

[Contact Formular](http://www.footyheadlines.com/p/footy-headlines-contact-form.html).
